

## **PROJECTS**

### **GROOVESHARK CHAT**

Oct 2014 - Dec 2014

INTERACTION DESIGNER

Real client based class project to integrate a chat feature into Grooveshark's current Interface. Design process involved user research, brainstorming, wireframing, and creating an interactive prototype. Final design solution was exhibited to Grooveshark development team and Computer Science department faculty and students.

MUNCHER Mar 2014 - Dec 2014

**DEVELOPER + DESIGNER + ARTIST** 

Self-initiated project created for the purpose of learning how to create mobile games for Android devices. Developed with the Cocos2d-x framework.

**PAPERCUTS** Jan 2013 – Apr 2013

TECHNICAL LEAD + LEVEL DESIGNER

Semester-long group project to familiarize students with the game design process. The game is 2D/3D Platformer developed with the Unity Engine. Final product was exhibited to faculty and students of the Computer Science department.

**SUPER SLIME BLOB** 

Jan 2010 – Aug 2010

DEVELOPER + DESIGNER + ARTIST

Exhibition project that started in high school and continued development past graduation. The game is a 2D Platformer created with the Microsoft XNA Game Studio.

# **EXPERIENCE**

**DEVELOPER INTERN** AT BIG PICTURE GAMES

*Jun 2013 – Aug 2013* Gainesville, FL

Worked with the Unity Engine on a game called Flaming Narwhal. Contributions to development include updating HUD and menu screens, and reorganizing structure of existing code.

**TEACHING ASSISTANT** 

Jan 2013 – Present Gainesville, FL

DEPARTMENT OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Courses: Programming Funamentals 1, Interactive Modeling and Animation Assisted three different professors with the following tasks: grading, leading weekly discussion sections, holding office hours, advising students, lecture planning, and generating quiz and examination questions.

#### JONATHAN LUCKA

APARTMENT NO. CITY. STATE ZIP

(\*\*\*)\*\*\* \*\*\*\* **PHONE** 

**EMAIL** JOZZLEO6@GMAIL.COM JLUCKA625.GITHUB.IO WEB

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in **Digital Arts and Sciences** University of Florida August 2010 – May 2015

## **AWARDS**

Top 100 out of 5000 **Spotify Code Quest** Feburary 2012

## SKII I SFT

Game Design **UI** Design Interaction Design 3D Modeling Graphic Design Web Design **Computer Graphics** 

## **TOOLSET**

**Unity Engine** Autodesk Maya Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Processing Java C/C++ HTML/CSS Javascript/jQuery Git **Balsamiq** InVision Microsoft Office